

# ABOUT ME

I gained leadership practice in manufacturing environment, therefore I can work very well and efficiently on complex problems within a team.

I've always been a progressive-minded man, attracted by technological advancement.

Thats why I want to experience what is it like to work as a programmer.

# Soft Skills

Analytical thinking

Problem solving

Critical thinking

Teamwork

Presentation

# Language

English

(intermediate)

# BÁLINT TÓTH

Budapest, XVIII. district +(36) 30 663 8889 tothbalint90@gmail.com



## EXPERIENCE

GREENFOX ACADEMY (2019-07 - 2019-12)

During the course my main language was **Java** and used **Spring framework** for building **web applications**, following the **MVC** design pattern. Later I switched to **C**# for the more advanced topics. For a real like project I was working with C# in **ASP.NET Core** environment for the last two months of the bootcamp.

### UNIT LEADER

(2018-02 - 2019-07)

My responsibilities and tasks as a Unit Leader:

- Lead and support of the lab team and coordinate of workflow.
- Achieve the required production program, re-plan of it if necessary.
- Recording production datas, running KPIs, making monthly reports.
- Performing technology development and optimization tasks.

#### TECHNICIAN

(2017-02 - 2018-01)

As a technician my responsibility was to:

- carrying out tasks related to general viral vaccine production (in aseptic working environment).
- proper handling of technical equipment in a high-responsibility work environment, production documentation, reporting.

## EDUCATION

Green Fox Academy

Junior Software Developer Computer Software Engineering (2019)

John von Neumann University

Quality Systems Engineer Bachelor of Engineering - BE (2017 - 2019)

University of Szeged

Biochemical Engineer Bachelor of Engineering - BE

(2014 - 2017)